<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Final Project on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</title>
    <link>/2018/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Final Project on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/proposal/</guid>
      <description>Propose a final project.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Proposal” Since the proposal is short, you can write your proposal in the comment. Alternatively attach a file or reference a text file in your repository. Assign the issue to the instructors. After receiving comments from the instructors, the student must reply in a comment to address these comments and suggestions.   Instructions The proposal should include the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draft Submission</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/draft-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/draft-submission/</guid>
      <description>Submit a draft with the current state of the research project. See the final project page for details on expectations and format.
No late assignments will be accepted. If no issue is opened, then the current state of the repository will be reviewed.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Draft submission” In the comment of the issue discuss the current state of the project, what is left to be done, and what problems the student has had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/peer_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 13:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/peer_review/</guid>
      <description>Review the assigned students project.
To submit:
Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Peer Review” Provide the peer review in the comments. Note that you can attach files to comments. Mention the instructors.  The reviewer should
Confirm that the code is reproducible Comment on the methodology and design of the analysis.  The reviewee should reply in a comment that addresses the comments of the reviewer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Submission</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/final-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 23:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/final-submission/</guid>
      <description>Submit the final research project. See the final project page for details on expectations and format.
No late assignments will be accepted. If no issue is opened, then the current state of the repository will be reviewed.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Final submission” In the comment of the issue indicate how you have resolved any and all issues raised by comments of the instructor or peer review.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>