<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>POLS/CS&amp;SS 503 (Spring 2018) on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</title>
    <link>/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in POLS/CS&amp;SS 503 (Spring 2018) on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/proposal/</guid>
      <description>Propose a final project.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Proposal” Since the proposal is short, you can write your proposal in the comment. Alternatively attach a file or reference a text file in your repository. Assign the issue to the instructors. After receiving comments from the instructors, the student must reply in a comment to address these comments and suggestions.   Instructions The proposal should include the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draft Submission</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/draft-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/draft-submission/</guid>
      <description>Submit a draft with the current state of the research project. See the final project page for details on expectations and format.
No late assignments will be accepted. If no issue is opened, then the current state of the repository will be reviewed.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Draft submission” In the comment of the issue discuss the current state of the project, what is left to be done, and what problems the student has had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/peer_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 13:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/peer_review/</guid>
      <description>Review the assigned students project.
To submit:
Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Peer Review” Provide the peer review in the comments. Note that you can attach files to comments. Mention the instructors.  The reviewer should
Confirm that the code is reproducible Comment on the methodology and design of the analysis.  The reviewee should reply in a comment that addresses the comments of the reviewer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Submission</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/final-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 23:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/final-submission/</guid>
      <description>Submit the final research project. See the final project page for details on expectations and format.
No late assignments will be accepted. If no issue is opened, then the current state of the repository will be reviewed.
Submission Open an issue on that student’s project repository, e.g. https://github.com/studnet/pols-503-2018-project/ titled “Final submission” In the comment of the issue indicate how you have resolved any and all issues raised by comments of the instructor or peer review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-11/</guid>
      <description>Finals week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-9/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-8/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>/2018/schedule/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/schedule/week-1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHANGELOG</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/changelog/</guid>
      <description> See the GitHub repository the history of changes.
2018-04-04  Add instructions for final project Add dates for project assignments to the schedule Add dates for assignments to schedule  2018-04-02  Remove old schedule / project  2018-03-30  Added readings for weeks 2&amp;ndash;10 to the schedule. Remove r4ds notes page  2018-03-27  Add office hours for Jeff and Calvin.  2018-03-26  Updated onboarding instructions.  2018-03-08  Initial draft of syllabus page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help with R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/help/</guid>
      <description>A good place to start is Rstudio’s guide for getting help with R
Asking for Help When asking for help with R it is important to at least
Include the exact code that you ran The error message that you got  Without the code and the error message it can be hard to impossible to diagnose the problem and provide a solution. Questions such as “This isn’t working” or even “I’m getting this error message” aren’t useful without the code and error message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git and GitHub</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git/</guid>
      <description>For quick introduction on learn how to use Version control within RStudio, I suggest the “Version Control” chapter of the Working with the RStudio IDE (Part 2) DataCamp course.
Relationship between GitHub and Local Git Projects  References  Jenny Bryan, Happy Git and GitHub for the useR DataCamp course Version Control with Git. This course requires shell knowledge, but the following two modules are useful.  Automated Version Control Using Git from RStudio  Simple guide to forks in GitHub and Git GitHub Help Git and GitHub videos for beginners from dataschool introduces git and GitHub via many videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git: Assignment Submission and Workflow</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git-assignment-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git-assignment-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Cloning, Pull Requests, Forking, Pulling, and Pushing See the Happy Git and GitHub for the useR chapter Fork a repo.
 Instructions Go to the course website, click Assignments.
 Scroll down to the Assignments section, click on the link to the assignment under Instructions and Submissions.
 Click on the Fork button to fork the repository to your GitHub account.
 Click Clone or download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/install/</guid>
      <description>Installing or Updating R Install R The R website is … special. Since you probably don’t know or care what a mirror is, here are links to the
 Go to the R Project website Choose the Download and install R your operation system:  Mac: Download R-3.4.3.pkg Windows: First click on base and then on Download R 3.4.3 for Windows    Upgrade R If you already have R installed, to check that you have the newest version of R, run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding for POLS 503</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Please complete the following before Wednesday, March 28, 2018.
Sign up for our Slack workplace, https://uwpolsmethods.slack.com/. We will use this for announcements, and asking and answering questions in this course. You should have received an invite. If not email the instructor to receive one.
 Tell us about yourself: Complete the pre-course survey. If you are registered for the course, you should have received an email. If not, you can find a link pinned on the #announcements channel of Slack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Articles and books references in this course. Download these references as bibtex file here.
Angrist, Joshua D, and Jörn-Steffen Pischke. 2010. “The Credibility Revolution in Empirical Economics: How Better Research Design Is Taking the Con Out of Econometrics.” Journal of Economic Perspectives 24 (2). American Economic Association:3–30. https://doi.org/10.1257/jep.24.2.3.
 Bailey, Michael A., Anton Strezhnev, and Erik Voeten. 2016. “Estimating Dynamic State Preferences from United Nations Voting Data.” Journal of Conflict Resolution 61 (2).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>